Guide to the Rabbi Arthur Schneier Papers TAM.694
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series I. Appeal of Conscience Foundation Material, 1964-2018, undated; 29 audiocassettes; 5 VHS; 52.75 Gigabytes in 6,985 computer files.; 32 Linear Feet in 4 record cartons, 59 manuscript boxes, 3 half manuscript boxes, 2.5 small flat boxes, 1 oversize flat box, and 2.5 media boxes.
  - Subseries I.B. Annual Awards Dinners and Luncheons, 1969-2018, undated; 11 audiocassettes; 2 VHS; 26.04 Gigabytes in 5,453 computer files.; 7 Linear Feet in 1 record carton, 15 manuscript boxes, 1 half manuscript box, 2 small flat boxes, and .5 media box.
    - 1979 AAD: Program and Guest List, 1 folder (Box 215, Folder 16)
    - 1979 AAD: Speech -- Schneier, Rabbi Arthur, 1 folder (Box 215, Folder 18)
    - 1979 AAD: Speeches, 1979, undated; 3 folders (Box 229, Folder 7, Box 247, Folder 19, Box 183, Folder 4)
    - 1979 AAD: Speeches and Press, 1 folder (Box 44, Folder 20)
    - 1979 AAD: Venue and Catering Expenses, 1 folder (Box 44, Folder 19)
    - 1980 AAD: Biographical File -- Recipient, undated; 1 folder (Box 44, Folder 1)
    - 1980 AAD: Correspondence, 2 folders (Box 44, Folder 5, 6)
    - 1980 AAD: Correspondence -- Entertainment, Catering, Venue, and Invitation Expenses, 1979-1980; 1 folder (Box 44, Folder 8)
    - 1980 AAD: Correspondence -- Invitations, 1 folder (Box 44, Folder 2)
    - 1980 AAD: Correspondence -- Thank You Letters to Donors, 1980-1981; 2 folders (Box 44, Folder 3, 4)
    - 1980 AAD: Formal Invitations, 1 folder (Box 8, Folder 72)
    - 1980 AAD: Media Advisory, undated; 1 folder (Box 44, Folder 9)
    - 1980 AAD: Photographs -- Recipient Malcolm Forbes, undated; 1 folder (Box 242, Folder 11)
    - 1980 AAD: Press, 1 folder (Box 44, Folder 14)
    - 1980 AAD: Seating Information and Lists of Guests, undated; 1 folder (Box 44, Folder 7)
    - 1980 AAD: Speeches, 2 folders (Box 247, Folder 20, Box 183, Folder 5)
    - 1981 AAD: Correspondence -- Thank You Message from Recipient, 1982; 1 folder (Box 260, Folder 10)
    - 1981 AAD: Photographs and Negatives, undated; 1 folder (Box 242, Folder 8)
    - 1981 AAD: Speeches, 2 folders (Box 247, Folder 21, Box 183, Folder 6)
    - 1982 AAD: Speech -- Schneier, Rabbi Arthur, 1 folder (Box 44, Folder 15)
    - 1982 AAD: Speeches, 2 folders (Box 247, Folder 22, Box 183, Folder 7)
    - 1983 AAD: Speeches, 2 folders (Box 247, Folder 23, Box 183, Folder 8)
    - 1984 AAD: Correspondence, 2 folders (Box 44, Folder 16, Box 258, Folder 17)
    - 1984 AAD: Note and Photographic Contact Sheets, 1984, undated; 2 folders (Box 201, Folder 1, 2)
    - 1984 AAD: Press, 1 folder (Box 218, Folder 3)
    - 1984 AAD: Speeches, 2 folders (Box 247, Folder 24, Box 183, Folder 9)
    - 1985 AAD: Correspondence, 1 folder (Box 207, Folder 16)
    - 1985 AAD: Invitation, 1 folder (Box 9, Folder 14)
    - 1985 AAD: Press, 1 folder (Box 160, Folder 12)
    - 1985 AAD: Speeches, 2 folders (Box 247, Folder 25, Box 183, Folder 10)
    - 1986 AAD: Correspondence, 2 folders (Box 207, Folder 15, Box 44, Folder 13)
    - 1986 AAD: Speeches, 2 folders (Box 248, Folder 9, Box 183, Folder 11)
    - 1987 AAD: Correspondence, 1 folder (Box 44, Folder 12)
    - 1987 AAD: Miklos Itinerary, 1 folder (Box 79, Folder 23)
    - 1987 AAD: Speeches, 2 folders (Box 248, Folder 10, Box 183, Folder 12)
    - 1988 AAD: Correspondence, 2 folders (Box 207, Folder 14, Box 44, Folder 11)
    - 1988 AAD: Speeches, 1 folder (Box 248, Folder 8)
    - 1989 AAD: Correspondence, 1 folder (Box 207, Folder 13)
    - 1989 AAD: Speeches, 2 folders (Box 248, Folder 5, Box 183, Folder 13)
    - 1989 AAL: Photographic Contact Sheets -- Recipient Richard von Weizsacker, undated; 1 folder (Box 120, Folder 17)
    - 1989 AAL: Photographs and Press -- Recipient Richard von Weizsacker, undated; 2 folders (Box 120, Folder 15, 16)
    - 1990 AAD: Correspondence, 1990-1991; 1 folder (Box 207, Folder 8)
    - 1990 AAD: Speeches, 2 folders (Box 248, Folder 6, Box 183, Folder 14)
    - 1991 AAD: Correspondence, 1991-1992; 1 folder (Box 207, Folder 9)
    - 1991 AAD: Photographs, Negatives, and Images -- Recipients Dick Cheney and Hans Dietrich Genscher, undated; 4 folders (Box 122, Folder 9-12)
    - 1991 AAD: Photographs and Photographic Contact Sheets -- Recipients Dick Cheney and Hans Dietrich Genscher, 1989, undated; 1 folder (Box 243, Folder 11)
    - 1991 AAD: Speeches, 2 folders (Box 248, Folder 4, Box 183, Folder 15)
    - 1992 AAD: Correspondence, 1 folder (Box 207, Folder 10)
    - 1992 AAD: Correspondence -- Requests for Best Wishes from Government Officials, 1 folder (Box 207, Folder 6)
    - 1992 AAD: Photographic Contact Sheets and Negatives, undated; 1 folder (Box 244, Folder 6)
    - 1992 AAD: Photographs, undated; 4 folders (Box 243, Folder 18, Box 244, Folder 1-3)
    - 1992 AAD: Photographs and Negatives, undated; 1 folder (Box 244, Folder 5)
    - 1992 AAD: Photographs and Sound Recording, 1992, undated; 1 folder (Box 244, Folder 4)
    - 1992 AAD: Press and Notes, 1 folder (Box 244, Folder 7)
    - 1992 AAD: Sound Recording (Box 255, Cassette 694.0041)
    - 1992 AAD: Speeches, 1 folder (Box 247, Folder 15)
    - 1993 AAD: Biographical Information -- Chairs, 1 folder (Box 16, Folder 10)
    - 1993 AAD: Correspondence, 3 folders (Box 16, Folder 3, Box 207, Folder 2, 11)
    - 1993 AAD: Correspondence -- Best Wishes from Government and Religious Leaders, 1 folder (Box 207, Folder 5)
    - 1993 AAD: Correspondence -- Caterer, 1 folder (Box 16, Folder 17)
    - 1993 AAD: Correspondence -- Chairs, 1 folder (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - 1993 AAD: Correspondence -- Complimentary Attendance Invitations, 1 folder (Box 16, Folder 5)
    - 1993 AAD: Correspondence -- Musicians, 1 folder (Box 16, Folder 16)
    - 1993 AAD: Correspondence -- Place Settings, Event Favors, and Videography, 1 folder (Box 16, Folder 14)
    - 1993 AAD: Correspondence -- Program Galleys, 1 folder (Box 16, Folder 15)
    - 1993 AAD: Correspondence and Biographical Information -- Speakers, 1 folder (Box 16, Folder 12)
    - 1993 AAD: Correspondence and Lists -- Dinner Committee, undated; 1 folder (Box 207, Folder 4)
    - 1993 AAD: Correspondence and Lists -- Honorary Chairs, 1 folder (Box 16, Folder 11)
    - 1993 AAD: Correspondence, Lists of Guests, and Speeches -- Recipient, 1 folder (Box 16, Folder 9)
    - 1993 AAD: Donor Contact Lists, 3 folders (Box 16, Folder 2, 4, 7)
    - 1993 AAD: Event Schedule, 1 folder (Box 207, Folder 1)
    - 1993 AAD: Lists of Guests, 1 folder (Box 16, Folder 6)
    - 1993 AAD: Notes, 1 folder (Box 207, Folder 3)
    - 1993 AAD: Photographs -- Presentation of Award to Patriarch Aleksy II in Private Ceremony, undated; 1 folder (Box 243, Folder 16)
    - 1993 AAD: Photographs -- Recipient, undated; 1 folder (Box 16, Folder 8)
    - 1993 AAD: Photographs and Images, undated; 5 folders (Box 123, Folder 15, 16, Box 243, Folder 13-15)
    - 1993 AAD: Photographs, Images, and Photographic Contact Sheets -- Presentation of Award to Patriarch Aleksy II in Private Ceremony, 1993, undated; 1 folder (Box 243, Folder 17)
    - 1993 AAD: Seating Lists and Charts, 1 folder (Box 16, Folder 13)
    - 1993 AAD: Speeches, 1 folder (Box 247, Folder 14)
    - 1993 AAD: Speeches and Newspaper Clipping, 1 folder (Box 207, Folder 7)
    - 1994 AAD: Correspondence, 1 folder (Box 207, Folder 12)
    - 1994 AAD: Photographs and Image -- Recipients President Menem of Argentina and John F. Smith, Jr., undated; 1 folder (Box 133, Folder 9)
    - 1994 AAD: Photographs and Images -- Recipients President Menem of Argentina and John F. Smith, Jr., undated; 1 folder (Box 133, Folder 11)
    - 1994 AAD: Photographs, Images, and Photographic Contact Sheets -- Recipients President Menem of Argentina and John F. Smith, Jr., 1994, undated; 1 folder (Box 128, Folder 8)
    - 1994 AAD: Photographs and Photographic Contact Sheets -- Recipients President Menem of Argentina and John F. Smith, Jr., undated; 1 folder (Box 133, Folder 8)
    - 1994 AAD: Speeches, 1 folder (Box 247, Folder 13)
    - 1994 AAL: Award, Entertainment, Gifts, and Photographer Information, 1 folder (Box 56, Folder 20)
    - 1994 AAL: Biographical Information -- Recipient, 1993-1994, undated; 1 folder (Box 56, Folder 3)
    - 1994 AAL: Complimentary Attendance Lists, 1 folder (Box 56, Folder 18)
    - 1994 AAL: Correspondence, 3 folders (Box 56, Folder 10, 17, Box 219, Folder 20)
    - 1994 AAL: Correspondence -- Best Wishes form Government and Business Leaders, 1 folder (Box 56, Folder 12)
    - 1994 AAL: Correspondence -- Chairs, 1 folder (Box 219, Folder 21)
    - 1994 AAL: Correspondence -- Invitations, 1 folder (Box 56, Folder 9)
    - 1994 AAL: Correspondence -- Possible Honorary Co-Chairs, 1992-1994; 1 folder (Box 56, Folder 2)
    - 1994 AAL: Correspondence -- Recipient, 1994-1995; 3 folders (Box 56, Folder 1, 7, 8)
    - 1994 AAL: Correspondence -- Requests for Best Wishes from Government Officials, 1 folder (Box 56, Folder 13)
    - 1994 AAL: Correspondence -- Thank You Letters, 1 folder (Box 220, Folder 1)
    - 1994 AAL: Correspondence and Contract -- Venue, 1 folder (Box 220, Folder 2)
    - 1994 AAL: Final Specification Sheet, 1 folder (Box 220, Folder 6)
    - 1994 AAL: Invitation and Reply Cards Layouts, 1 folder (Box 220, Folder 8)
    - 1994 AAL: List of Awards Committee Members, undated; 1 folder (Box 56, Folder 16)
    - 1994 AAL: Lists of Donors, 1992-1994; 1 folder (Box 56, Folder 15)
    - 1994 AAL: Lists of Guests, 1 folder (Box 219, Folder 22)
    - 1994 AAL: Lists of Possible Invitees, 1993-1994; 1 folder (Box 56, Folder 14)
    - 1994 AAL: Lists of Responses to Invitations, 1 folder (Box 56, Folder 19)
    - 1994 AAL: Notes, 1994, undated; 1 folder (Box 220, Folder 3)
    - 1994 AAL: Notes -- Board, undated; 1 folder (Box 56, Folder 11)
    - 1994 AAL: Press, 1 folder (Box 220, Folder 4)
    - 1994 AAL: Program Layout, 1 folder (Box 220, Folder 9)
    - 1994 AAL: Schedule and List of Invitees to Private Event, 1 folder (Box 220, Folder 5)
    - 1994 AAL: Seating Information, 1994, undated; 1 folder (Box 220, Folder 10)
    - 1994 AAL: Speech -- Recipient, 1 folder (Box 219, Folder 23)
    - 1994 AAL: Speeches, 1994, undated; 1 folder (Box 220, Folder 7)
    - 1995 AAD: Biographical Information -- Chair, 1 folder (Box 57, Folder 9)
    - 1995 AAD: Biographical Information -- Recipient, 1995, undated; 2 folders (Box 57, Folder 3, 6)
    - 1995 AAD: Correspondence, 1 folder (Box 57, Folder 13)
    - 1995 AAD: Correspondence -- Best Wishes from Religious and Government Officials, 1994-1995; 1 folder (Box 220, Folder 13)
    - 1995 AAD: Correspondence -- Chairs, 2 folders (Box 57, Folder 10, 14)
    - 1995 AAD: Correspondence -- Flourist and Photographer, 1994-1995; 1 folder (Box 57, Folder 15)
    - 1995 AAD: Correspondence -- Honorary Chairs, 1995-1996; 1 folder (Box 57, Folder 11)
    - 1995 AAD: Correspondence -- Invitation and Reply Layout, 1 folder (Box 57, Folder 20)
    - 1995 AAD: Correspondence -- Possible Honorary Chairs, 1 folder (Box 57, Folder 7)
    - 1995 AAD: Correspondence -- Recipient, 1995-1996; 2 folders (Box 57, Folder 2, 5)
    - 1995 AAD: Correspondence -- Save the Date Letter, 1 folder (Box 220, Folder 19)
    - 1995 AAD: Correspondence -- Thank You Letters, 1 folder (Box 220, Folder 18)
    - 1995 AAD: Final Specification Sheet, 1 folder (Box 220, Folder 16)
    - 1995 AAD: Fundraising Reports, 1 folder (Box 57, Folder 19)
    - 1995 AAD: Lists of Guests, undated; 1 folder (Box 57, Folder 12)
    - 1995 AAD: Notes, 1995, undated; 1 folder (Box 57, Folder 17)
    - 1995 AAD: Notes and Instructions -- Dresbach, Karen, 1995, undated; 1 folder (Box 57, Folder 18)
    - 1995 AAD: Photographs -- Recipients President of Brazil Fernando Cardoso and Helmut Maucher, 1995, undated; 1 folder (Box 130, Folder 9)
    - 1995 AAD: Photographs and Negatives, undated; 6 folders (Box 123, Folder 1, 2, 4-7)
    - 1995 AAD: Photographs and Negatives -- Schneier, Rabbi Arthur with Recipients Brazil President Fernando Henrique Cardoso and Helmut Maucher, 1995, undated; 1 folder (Box 123, Folder 3)
    - 1995 AAD: Photographs and Sheet Music -- Recipient, undated; 1 folder (Box 57, Folder 1)
    - 1995 AAD: Press, 2 folders (Box 220, Folder 11, 12)
    - 1995 AAD: Press Kit, 1 folder (Box 57, Folder 21)
    - 1995 AAD: Program, 1 folder (Box 176, Folder 19)
    - 1995 AAD: Seating Information, 1995, undated; 1 folder (Box 220, Folder 15)
    - 1995 AAD: Sequence of Events, 1 folder (Box 220, Folder 14)
    - 1995 AAD: Sound Recording (Box 206, Cassette 694.0013)
    - 1995 AAD: Speech -- Recipients, 1 folder (Box 57, Folder 4)
    - 1995 AAD: Speeches, 1 folder (Box 247, Folder 12)
    - 1995 AAD: Speeches -- Chairs, undated; 1 folder (Box 57, Folder 8)
    - 1995 AAD: Speeches -- Recipients, 1 folder (Box 220, Folder 17)
    - 1995 AAD: Venue Information, 1995, undated; 1 folder (Box 57, Folder 16)
    - 1996 AAD: Biographical Information and Correspondence -- Recipient, 1996, undated; 3 folders (Box 220, Folder 20, 21, Box 58, Folder 1)
    - 1996 AAD: Correspondence, 2 folders (Box 58, Folder 5, Box 221, Folder 3)
    - 1996 AAD: Correspondence -- Best Wishes from Government Officials, 1 folder (Box 58, Folder 16)
    - 1996 AAD: Correspondence -- Caterers, 1 folder (Box 58, Folder 6)
    - 1996 AAD: Correspondence -- Chairs, 2 folders (Box 58, Folder 3, Box 221, Folder 1)
    - 1996 AAD: Correspondence -- Chairs, Administrators, and Board Members, 1 folder (Box 58, Folder 14)
    - 1996 AAD: Correspondence -- Flourist and Photographer, 1 folder (Box 58, Folder 11)
    - 1996 AAD: Correspondence -- Gifts for Guests, 1 folder (Box 58, Folder 10)
    - 1996 AAD: Correspondence -- Guest List, 1 folder (Box 58, Folder 12)
    - 1996 AAD: Correspondence -- Honorary Chair Invitations and Replies, 1 folder (Box 58, Folder 2)
    - 1996 AAD: Correspondence -- Invitation and Lists of Guests Invited to Sit on the Dias, 1 folder (Box 58, Folder 8)
    - 1996 AAD: Correspondence -- Invitation Printing Services, 1 folder (Box 58, Folder 20)
    - 1996 AAD: Correspondence -- Invitations, 1 folder (Box 221, Folder 2)
    - 1996 AAD: Correspondence -- Musicians, 1 folder (Box 58, Folder 15)
    - 1996 AAD: Correspondence -- Possible Chairs, 1 folder (Box 58, Folder 4)
    - 1996 AAD: Correspondence -- Program Printers, 1 folder (Box 58, Folder 19)
    - 1996 AAD: Correspondence -- Requests for Best Wishes from Government Officials, 1 folder (Box 58, Folder 22)
    - 1996 AAD: Correspondence -- Security, 1 folder (Box 58, Folder 24)
    - 1996 AAD: Correspondence -- Thank You Letters, 1 folder (Box 58, Folder 28)
    - 1996 AAD: Correspondence -- Venue and Caterer Information, 1 folder (Box 58, Folder 13)
    - 1996 AAD: Correspondence and Contract -- Event Planner, 1 folder (Box 58, Folder 9)
    - 1996 AAD: Correspondence and Lists of Guests -- High Profile Women, 1 folder (Box 58, Folder 31)
    - 1996 AAD: Correspondence and Photographs -- Photographer, 1 folder (Box 58, Folder 18)
    - 1996 AAD: Fundraising Reports, 1 folder (Box 58, Folder 30)
    - 1996 AAD: List of Guests Who Got Complimentary Dinners, 1 folder (Box 58, Folder 7)
    - 1996 AAD: List of Past Donors, 1990-1995; 1 folder (Box 221, Folder 5)
    - 1996 AAD: Lists of Possible Guests, 1996, undated; 1 folder (Box 221, Folder 4)
    - 1996 AAD: Lists of VIP Guests, 1 folder (Box 58, Folder 29)
    - 1996 AAD: Notes, 1 folder (Box 58, Folder 17)
    - 1996 AAD: Press, 1996, undated; 1 folder (Box 58, Folder 21)
    - 1996 AAD: Save the Date Cards, 1 folder (Box 58, Folder 23)
    - 1996 AAD: Seating Information, 1996, undated; 1 folder (Box 58, Folder 27)
    - 1996 AAD: Sequence of Events and Sound Recording Contract, 1 folder (Box 58, Folder 25)
    - 1996 AAD: Sound Recording, undated (Box 206, Cassette 694.0014)
    - 1996 AAD: Speeches, 2 folders (Box 58, Folder 26, Box 247, Folder 11)
    - 1997 AAD: Biographical Information -- Recipient, 1997, undated; 1 folder (Box 94, Folder 3)
    - 1997 AAD: Correspondence, 1996-1997
      - Digital Files, 1996-1997; TW_TAM_694_ER_96
      - Paper Files (Box 94, Folder 10)
    - 1997 AAD: Correspondence -- ACF Members of the Board and Advisory Council, 1996; 1 folder (Box 94, Folder 11)
    - 1997 AAD: Correspondence -- Best Wishes from Political and Religious Leaders, 1996-1997; 1 folder (Box 234, Folder 14)
    - 1997 AAD: Correspondence -- Chairs, 1996-1997; 2 folders (Box 94, Folder 6, 9)
    - 1997 AAD: Correspondence -- Complimentary Attendance Invitations, 1996-1997; 1 folder (Box 94, Folder 16)
    - 1997 AAD: Correspondence -- Gifts for Guests, 1 folder (Box 94, Folder 22)
    - 1997 AAD: Correspondence -- Honorary Chairs, 1996-1997; 1 folder (Box 94, Folder 5)
    - 1997 AAD: Correspondence -- Recipient, 1996-1997; 1 folder (Box 94, Folder 4)
    - 1997 AAD: Correspondence -- Thank You Letters, 1 folder (Box 234, Folder 11)
    - 1997 AAD: Correspondence -- Wine Donors, 1 folder (Box 234, Folder 10)
    - 1997 AAD: Correspondence and Contract -- Venue and Caterer, 1996-1997; 1 folder (Box 94, Folder 18)
    - 1997 AAD: Correspondence, Contract, and Sheet Music -- Musicians, 1997, undated; 1 folder (Box 94, Folder 20)
    - 1997 AAD: Correspondence and Lists of Possible Corporate Sponsors -- Executive Chair, 1 folder (Box 94, Folder 8)
    - 1997 AAD: Correspondence and Photograph -- Best Wishes from Political and Religious Leaders, 1997, undated; 1 folder (Box 94, Folder 24)
    - 1997 AAD: Correspondence and Sound Recording -- Audiovisual Company, 1 folder (Box 94, Folder 13)
    - 1997 AAD: Correspondence and Table Seating -- Dais Invitees, 1 folder (Box 94, Folder 14)
    - 1997 AAD: Final Specification Sheet, 1 folder (Box 94, Folder 1)
    - 1997 AAD: Fundraising Report, 1 folder (Box 94, Folder 19)
    - 1997 AAD: Guest List, 1 folder (Box 94, Folder 17)
    - 1997 AAD: Invitation, Reply Card, and Letterhead Layouts, 1 folder (Box 234, Folder 13)
    - 1997 AAD: Lists of Potential Chairs, undated (Box 94, Folder 7)
    - 1997 AAD: Notes, 1996; 1 folder (Box 94, Folder 21)
    - 1997 AAD: Photographic Film Rolls, 1997, undated; 1 folder (Box 136, Folder 12)
    - 1997 AAD: Photographs -- Recipient, undated; 1 folder (Box 94, Folder 2)
    - 1997 AAD: Press, 1997, undated; 2 folders (Box 94, Folder 23, Box 234, Folder 12)
    - 1997 AAD: Program, 2 folders (Box 94, Folder 26, Box 176, Folder 18)
    - 1997 AAD: Seating Information, 1 folder (Box 94, Folder 27)
    - 1997 AAD: Sequence of Events, Contract, and Correspondence -- Event Planner, 1 folder (Box 94, Folder 15)
    - 1997 AAD: Sound Recording (Box 206, Cassette 694.0020)
    - 1997 AAD: Speeches, 4 folders (Box 94, Folder 25, Box 234, Folder 9, Box 247, Folder 10, Box 176, Folder 27)
    - 1998 AAD: Audio and Video Recording Information, 1 folder (Box 221, Folder 11)
    - 1998 AAD: Biographical Information -- Recipient, 1998, undated; 1 folder (Box 59, Folder 30)
    - 1998 AAD: Biographical Information and Correspondence -- Chair, 1998, undated; 1 folder (Box 221, Folder 6)
    - 1998 AAD: Catering Information, 1 folder (Box 221, Folder 12)
    - 1998 AAD: Correspondence, 1997-1998; 1 folder (Box 221, Folder 9)
    - 1998 AAD: Correspondence -- Acceptance Letters, 1 folder (Box 221, Folder 10)
    - 1998 AAD: Correspondence -- Best Wishes from Government Officials, 1 folder (Box 221, Folder 18)
    - 1998 AAD: Correspondence -- Chairs, 1 folder (Box 221, Folder 7)
    - 1998 AAD: Correspondence -- Complimentary Attendance Invitations, 1-11 folder (Box 222, Folder 5)
    - 1998 AAD: Correspondence -- Honorary Chairs, 1997-1998; 1 folder (Box 221, Folder 16)
    - 1998 AAD: Correspondence -- Possible Chairs, 1 folder (Box 221, Folder 8)
    - 1998 AAD: Correspondence -- Recipient, 1997-1998; 1 folder (Box 59, Folder 29)
    - 1998 AAD: Correspondence -- Thank You Letters, 1 folder (Box 222, Folder 4)
    - 1998 AAD: Event Planner Contract and List of Guests, 1 folder (Box 221, Folder 13)
    - 1998 AAD: Final Specification Sheet, 1 folder (Box 59, Folder 28)
    - 1998 AAD: Fundraising Report, 1 folder (Box 221, Folder 20)
    - 1998 AAD: Guest List, 1 folder (Box 221, Folder 15)
    - 1998 AAD: Invitation, 1 folder (Box 221, Folder 17)
    - 1998 AAD: Lists of Complimentary Attendance Guests, 1998, undated; 1 folder (Box 221, Folder 14)
    - 1998 AAD: Photocopies of Photographs -- Speakers, Recipient, Rabbi Arthur Schneier, Chairs, and Guests, undated; 1 folder (Box 221, Folder 19)
    - 1998 AAD: Photographs -- Recipient Indian President Kocheril Narayanan, undated; 2 folders (Box 239, Folder 15, 16)
    - 1998 AAD: Photographs and Photographic Contact Sheets -- Recipient Indian President Kocheril Narayanan, undated; 1 folder (Box 245, Folder 1)
    - 1998 AAD: Press, 1 folder (Box 221, Folder 21)
    - 1998 AAD: Program, 1 folder (Box 221, Folder 22)
    - 1998 AAD: Reception Lists of Guests, undated; 1 folder (Box 221, Folder 23)
    - 1998 AAD: Seating Information, 1998, undated; 1 folder (Box 222, Folder 1)
    - 1998 AAD: Sequence of Events, 1 folder (Box 222, Folder 2)
    - 1998 AAD: Sound Recording (Box 206, Cassette 694.0015)
    - 1998 AAD: Speech -- Recipient President K.R. Narayanan of India, 1 folder (Box 247, Folder 9)
    - 1998 AAD: Speeches, 1 folder (Box 222, Folder 3)
    - 1999 AAD: Biographical Information -- Recipient, 1999, undated; 2 folders (Box 59, Folder 12, 14)
    - 1999 AAD: Catering Information, 1 folder (Box 59, Folder 2)
    - 1999 AAD: Correspondence, 1998-1999; 1 folder (Box 59, Folder 1)
    - 1999 AAD: Correspondence -- Acceptance Letters, 1 folder (Box 59, Folder 16)
    - 1999 AAD: Correspondence -- Best Wishes from Government Officials, 1 folder (Box 59, Folder 8)
    - 1999 AAD: Correspondence -- Chairs, 1 folder (Box 59, Folder 15)
    - 1999 AAD: Correspondence -- Complimentary Attendance Invitations, 1 folder (Box 59, Folder 26)
    - 1999 AAD: Correspondence -- Possible Honorary Chairs, 1 folder (Box 59, Folder 6)
    - 1999 AAD: Correspondence -- Recipient, 1 folder (Box 59, Folder 13)
    - 1999 AAD: Correspondence -- Thank You Letters, 1 folder (Box 59, Folder 25)
    - 1999 AAD: Correspondence and Files -- Audiovisual Recording Company, 1 folder (Box 94, Folder 12)
    - 1999 AAD: Correspondence and Lists -- Declines, 1 folder (Box 59, Folder 17)
    - 1999 AAD: Correspondence and Photographs -- Gifts for Guests and Flowers, 1999, undated; 1 folder (Box 59, Folder 4)
    - 1999 AAD: Correspondence and Sound Recording -- Musicians, 1 folder (Box 59, Folder 10)
    - 1999 AAD: Event Planner Contract, 1998-1999; 1 folder (Box 59, Folder 27)
    - 1999 AAD: Final Specification Sheet, 1 folder (Box 59, Folder 22)
    - 1999 AAD: Fundraising Report, 1 folder (Box 59, Folder 9)
    - 1999 AAD: Guest Lists, 1999, undated; 1 folder (Box 59, Folder 5)
    - 1999 AAD: Invitation and Lists of Guests Sitting on the Dias, 1999, undated; 1 folder (Box 59, Folder 3)
    - 1999 AAD: Letterhead, 1 folder (Box 59, Folder 11)
    - 1999 AAD: Lists of Possible Guests, 1 folder (Box 59, Folder 24)
    - 1999 AAD: Press, 1998-1999; 1 folder (Box 59, Folder 19)
    - 1999 AAD: Public Relations Material, 1999, undated; 1 folder (Box 59, Folder 18)
    - 1999 AAD: Programs and Guest List, 1 folder (Box 59, Folder 20)
    - 1999 AAD: Seating Information, undated; 1 folder (Box 59, Folder 21)
    - 1999 AAD: Speeches, 1 folder (Box 59, Folder 23)
    - 1999 AAD: Speeches -- Recipients and Speakers, 1 folder (Box 247, Folder 8)
    - 1999 AAD: Transcription, TW_TAM_694_ER_40
    - 1999 AAD: Venue Information, 1 folder (Box 59, Folder 7)
    - 2000 AAD: Award Information, 1995-2000, undated; 1 folder (Box 222, Folder 6)
    - 2000 AAD: Correspondence, 1999-2000; 1 folder (Box 60, Folder 3)
    - 2000 AAD: Correspondence -- Acceptance Letters, 1 folder (Box 224, Folder 5)